{
    "id": "d5810473297b42ef96460d916d6ee962",
    "title": "Many or Much",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "It has been raining for ………………. days.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "49e42b12d7554c988107ae7deb8be08c"
        },
        {
            "question": "We didn’t do ……………….. work yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "54fc3024689846a3ad6578ee5d213f23"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has …………………. friends.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a9b38245eda9417bbf819bdef56534e3"
        },
        {
            "question": "A small car does not use ………………. fuel.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b321c2db4d104fa3a179a052e97a3464"
        },
        {
            "question": "There aren’t ……………… apples on the tree.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e8fe0c98565e45d79a1b3f58c4894f13"
        },
        {
            "question": "How ……………… money do you need?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7e0be7918fce4f7a9eb1ee483cf2879c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have been to Australia ……………….. times.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a319907626384d0eb64c0c2a9adb289d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t know ………………. about computers.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "51d2226fbb074a13bd582129c89a9e82"
        },
        {
            "question": "How ………………. people are there waiting outside?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cefb1d420f934c139b3a4b6ae5132a2a"
        },
        {
            "question": "He can speak ………………. languages.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2af7d53d6d9a44babf61108909c966b9"
        },
        {
            "question": "There isn’t …………………. water in this pond.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "48bd3f855fb644a492d7d5ec58abfa84"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have to hurry. I don’t have ………………… time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "92e3c942d0e849409e21c69e6c3c2583"
        }
    ]
}